<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Genero15</string>

    <string name="connect_to_internet">Connect To Internet!!!</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_discroll_view">DiscrollViewActivity</string>

<string name="tnc">
    1. You will earn 1 pt. for 1 share.\n
    2. Share your referral code with the other person to increase your earnings.\n
    3. You can get many cool stuff for free using these earnings like free events, passes and even free concert starring Falak Shabir.\n
    4. In case of any dispute, the decision taken by Genero committee will be final.
</string>

    <string name="title1">Title 1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_event">EventActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_core_team">CoreTeam</string>
    <string name="title_activity_facebook">FacebookActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_club">ClubActivity</string>

    <string name="action_hide">Hide Panel</string>
    <string name="action_show">Show Panel</string>
    <string name="action_anchor_enable">Enable Anchor Point</string>
    <string name="action_anchor_disable">Disable Anchor Point</string>

    <string name="title_activity_pseudo_main">PseudoMain</string>
    <string name="title_activity_particulare_event">ParticulareEventActivity</string>
    <string name="text">Squid blog crucifix Marfa, consectetur vero placeat mixtape. Non seitan sriracha eu, do Banksy fashion axe cred qui vegan delectus consequat Helvetica mollit. XOXO gluten-free disrupt, gastropub officia cliche chillwave hella pop-up. Fixie swag raw denim, YOLO craft beer assumenda occupy veniam photo booth pug consectetur next level Portland tote bag +1. Mlkshk PBR aliquip placeat Wes Anderson.</string>
    <string name="title">My Description</string>
    <string name="context_menu">Context menu</string>

    <string name="about_genero">Genero is the Annual Techo Cultural Feast of The ABES ENGINEERING COLLEGE hosted each year to celebrate the blend of technology and culture. Our college has been organizing GENERO for the last several years. It has organized earlier GENEROs on a very big scale and Thousands of Students took part in these mega events.This year we are expecting still better participation from various colleges all over India like from IIT\'s, NIT\'s and other universities.\n\nThis time we have taken up the theme of myths , mysteries and paradoxes existing in the world.\n\n  We on behalf of the college try to honor the spirit of our college as well as the entire community of technocrats.\n\n  For any Queries Regarding Genero mail us at genero@abes.ac.in\n\n\n </string>

    <string name="about_abes">ABES Engineering College is a manifestation of academic heritage with strong belief in “Guru-Shishya Parampara”. At this temple of learning, the focus is on human values, academic excellence, and composite personality development programs for enhancing the potential of individual students, enriching human values, and upholding the Indian value system- all acting in unison as a vehicle for growth at the national and international level, thereby making it a “student driven” institute of higher learning.\n\nSpread in over 64000 square meters, the institute has more than 80 state-of-the-art lecture theaters and 7 seminar halls equipped with LCD projector and PA system, 3 conference rooms and 1 state-of-the-art theater auditorium with a seating capacity of five hundred.\n\n\n</string>

    <string name="url_cultural">http://s19.postimg.org/4cbz6o1hf/cultural.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_cs">http://s8.postimg.org/ajjle8rl1/techcs1.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_ec">http://s11.postimg.org/52yzx4ysz/techec1.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_literary">http://s19.postimg.org/ec6vmkcqr/Illuminatus2.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_me">http://s19.postimg.org/4g5smx6yr/techme2.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_special">http://s23.postimg.org/bc7m8bcvv/BOB2.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_ce">http://s30.postimg.org/y20x64nip/tech_civill1.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_informals">http://s19.postimg.org/kom0wefsz/informals2.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_drama">http://s19.postimg.org/eri5fkyo3/DRAMATICS3.jpg</string>
    <string name="url_gaming">http://s29.postimg.org/vgc1wdr53/e_gaming1.jpg</string>


    <string name="about_special">this is description about SPECIAL.</string>


    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">ContactUs</string>


    <!--cultural .............................................................   -->

    <string name="about_cultural">this is description about CULTURAL.</string>
    <string-array name="cultural_1">
        <item>Solo Singing</item>
        <item>\n
            Solo singing is a musical composition for a single voice or instrument with or without accompaniment.\n
            It is the biggest chance for everyone to come up with the melodious voices on the stage.\n
            After all, talents are not meant to be hidden.\n
        </item>
        <item>\n
        &#8226; Maximum 2:30 minutes will be given for the performance.\n
        &#8226; Song shall be selected by the participant.\n
        &#8226; Song shall be performed without referring to any written lyrics.\n
        &#8226; Song shall be comprised of lyrics from mostly a Bollywood /Hollywood movie/album song.\n
        &#8226; Instrument or karaoke is optional.\n
        &#8226; Participant will have to register the song until half an hour before the event starts.\n
        &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
        &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all participants.
        </item>
        <item>
            15 OCTOBER\n
        10:00AM to 12:00PM

        </item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226; Trishna Sheoran - 9582049435\n
        &#8226; Rajat Jain - 9971447762</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cultural_2">
        <item>Solo Dance</item>
        <item>
            Solo dance is performed by an individual on the sound track as per the participant’s choice.\n
            *DIFFERENT SONGS SHOULD BE SELECTED FOR BOTH THE ROUNDS *
        </item>
        <item>
            (Round 1): \n
            &#8226; Audition round Participants can perform on any Bollywood/Hollywood/album/fusion songs.
            &#8226; Maximum 2:00 minutes will be given to perform.\n
            &#8226; No Props or costume or any material will be provided by the host college.\n
            &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Participant will have to submit the song half an hour before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all teams.\n
            (Round 2):\n
            &#8226; 10 participants will be shortlisted for the second round.\n
            &#8226; Participant can perform on any Bollywood /Hollywood/album/fusion songs.\n
            &#8226; Maximum 5:00 minutes will be given to perform.\n
            &#8226; No Props or costume or any material will be provided by the host college.\n
            &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Participant will have to submit the song until half an hour before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all teams.\n
        </item>
        <item>
        17 October\n
        10:00AM to 1:00PM</item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226; Priya Jain - 9654674267\n
              &#8226; Shivam Bansal - 9971492290</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cultural_3">
        <item>Group Dance</item>
        <item>

            This is your chance to show the unity of your team.\n
            Group dance competitions are designed to showcase the teamwork of a dancing talent.\n
            Show your creativity with the companionship of your dancing team with your tremendous performances.
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; At least 4 members team is required.\n
            &#8226; 4- 6 minutes max. will be given to perform.\n
            &#8226; No Props or costume or any material will be provided by the host college.\n
            &#8226; Participant will have to submit the song until half an hour before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all teams.
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n
        1:00PM to 4:00PM
        </item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226; Hitashee - 9953607557\n
              &#8226; Ankush Dhingra - 8586011180</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cultural_4">
        <item>INSTRUMENTAL</item>
        <item>
            The Musical Instrument Competition is designed to show how extraordinary ideas have the potential \n
            to change the way music is made and experienced.\n
            Entries are varied and creative, challenging the way instruments and music making have traditionally worked.
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226; Participants can perform with any instrument of their choice.\n
        &#8226; Maximum 3:00 minutes will be given for the performance\n
        &#8226; Only single instrument can be played at a time.\n
        &#8226; Participant will have to register the song until half an hour before the event starts.\n
        &#8226; No instrument or any material will be provided by the host college.\n
        &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
        &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all participants.
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n
        11:00AM to 1:00PM</item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226; Anshdha - 971748844\n
            &#8226; Anshul - 7838531667</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cultural_5">
        <item>Face-Off</item>
        <item>
          This competition provides students with a platform from which they can showcase the best of dance talent.\n
            Face Off has proven and still is one of the most anticipated competition of the dancing society.
        </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Pairing of the participants will be done through slips.\n
            &#8226; Maximum 3:00 minutes will be provided to each pair.\n
            &#8226; No Props or costume or any material will be provided by the host college.\n
            &#8226; If any queries then the participant must clear it before the event starts.\n
            &#8226; Decision of Judges will be final and binding on all teams.
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n
              10:00AM to 12:00PM</item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226; Sakshi Sharma - 9910747768\n
              &#8226; Vaibhav Singh - 888229079</item>


    </string-array>


    <!-- Tech cs  ........................................................ -->
    <string name="about_cs">this is description about CS.</string>
    <string-array name="cs_1">
       <item>Myths-n-Code\n
             Theme Based Coding</item>
       <item>
           &#8226; No. Of Rounds: 1\n

&#8226; Type: Individual as well as team Event (2 members)\n

&#8226; Description: This event will consist of simple coding questions but in

order to get access to these questions, you need to solve a few puzzles

related to some myths and mysteries. Internet usage is allowed.\n

&#8226; Type: Mystery related puzzles\n

&#8226; Time Limit: 2:00 hrs.\n

&#8226; Languages: C/C++/JAVA\n

&#8226; Winning Criteria: Only two winners will be decided at the end of event

from all the languages combined.\n
       </item>
       <item>
          &#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those

having less points but completed in less time\n

&#8226; Partially submitted test cases are counted and are checked after

the contest again for verification.\n

&#8226; Partially Submitted test cases have points equivalent to number

of test cases passed.\n

&#8226; Indulgence in any indisciplinary activity or usage of unfair means

will lead to cancellation of candidature.\n

&#8226; If two teams have same points then completion time will be

considered as tie breaker.\n

&#8226; Any team has to explain his logic and approach for a particular

question if any doubt is raised.\n

&#8226; Number of wrong attempts are counted and will be used for tie

breaker.\n

       </item>
        <item>16 October\n
            3:00PM to 5:00PM</item>
        <item>A-Block Basement Lab 1 - Lab 8 and LT 1-4</item>
        <item>&#8226; Vipul Sharma - 9953744250</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cs_2">
            <item>Quizzie\n
Mysterious Quiz</item>
       <item>
          &#8226; Description: This event will consist of hypothetical mysteries with some
hidden hints related to some tool or technology. The participants need
to find out the same in order to win.
Internet usage is allowed.\n
&#8226;No. Of Rounds: 1\n
&#8226;Type: Individual Event\n
&#8226;Round 1:\n
&#8226;Type: Mystery Quiz based on latest technologies.\n
&#8226;Time Limit: 1:30 hr.\n
&#8226;No. of questions: 20\n
&#8226;Winning Criteria: Only two winners will be decided at the end.\n      </item>
       <item>&#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those
having less points but completed in less time\n
&#8226; Usage of any unfair means or indulgence in any indisciplinary
activity through any means will lead to cancellation of
candidature.\n
&#8226; If two teams have same points then number of wrong answers
will be considered as tie breaker.\n
&#8226; If wrong answers are not satisfactory for tie breaking then a tie
breaker round will be conducted among the teams.\n
       </item>
        <item>15 October\n
        1:00PM to 3:00PM</item>
        <item>A-Block Basement Lab 1 - Lab 8 and LT 1-4</item>
        <item>&#8226;Anubhav Gupta - 8791632180\n
                &#8226;Himanshu Rajput - 8750612404</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cs_3">
            <item>INNOVATIA\n
A Development Challenge</item>
       <item>
          &#8226;No. Of Rounds: 1\n
&#8226;Type: Individual as well as team event (upto 4 members).\n
&#8226;Description: In this event, some topics related to the theme will be
given to the participants. They have to choose a single topic and create
any application related to it, which may be a web application, android
app or any other innovative application. The participants will have to
report at the start and end of the event. They will get 2 days to
complete their application and they can make it at their homes. The
idea behind the application, its proximity to the theme and the look
and feel of the application will serve as the criteria of evaluation.\n
&#8226;Round 1:\n
&#8226;Type: Developing application\n
&#8226;Time Limit: 1 day\n
&#8226;Winning Criteria: Only two winners will be decided at the end of event
and decision of judges will be the final decision.\n       </item>
       <item>&#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those
having fewer points.\n
&#8226; Usage of any unfair means or indulgence in any indisciplinary
activity through any means will lead to cancellation of
candidature.\n
&#8226; The participants can use online templates or any other resources
but not the complete code.\n
&#8226; The participants will have to follow strict time schedules, failing
which may lead to cancellation of candidature\n
       </item>
        <item>All Three days till 6 pm
        </item>
        <item>Seminar Hall - 4 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Aditi Sharma  -  9717057864</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cs_4">
            <item>CODEZONE\n
Make The Code</item>
       <item>
       &#8226;Description:
It is an online coding event where participants will be provided with
some problem statements and they have to design (code) the solution
using programming languages of their choice.\n
&#8226;No. Of Rounds: 2\n
&#8226;Type: Team (2 members) as well as Individual Event.\n
&#8226;Languages: C / C++ / JAVA\n
&#8226;Round 1:\n
&#8226;Time Limit: 2 hrs.\n
&#8226;Progress Criteria: Only Top 25% of total teams will be eligible for
second round, based on the results from round 1, and calculated using
no. of submitted questions (full / partial test cases) in minimum time.\n
&#8226;Round 2:\n
&#8226;Time Limit: 3 hrs.</item>
       <item>&#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those
having less points but completed in less time\n
&#8226; Partially submitted test cases are counted and are checked after
the contest again for verification.\n
&#8226; Partially Submitted test cases have points equivalent to number
of test cases passed.\n
&#8226; Usage of mobile phones and Internet is prohibited; any
participant found indulging in any such activity will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; Indulgence in any indisciplinary activity or usage of unfair means
will lead to cancellation of candidature.\n
&#8226; If two teams have same points then completion time will be
considered as tie breaker.\n
&#8226; Any team has to explain his logic and approach for a particular
question if any doubt is raised.\n
&#8226; Numbers of wrong attempts are counted and will be used for tie
breaker.\n
       </item>
        <item>&#8226;Round 1:\n
              15 October \n
        10:00AM to 1:00PM\n
        &#8226;Round 2:\n
        16 October \n
        11:00AM - 2:00PM</item>
        <item>A-Block Basement Lab 1 - Lab 8 and LT 1-4</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shubham Roy - 7838860845</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cs_5">
            <item>CODEBREAKER\n
Debug The Code</item>
       <item>
      &#8226;No. Of Rounds: 1\n
&#8226;Type: Team (2 members) as well as individual event.\n
&#8226;Description: In this event participants will have to correct an already
provided code (erroneous), without changing the core logic and
functionality. The type of probable errors could be
syntax/semantics/runtime.\n
&#8226;Type: Lab event\n
&#8226;Time Limit: 2 hrs.\n
&#8226;Languages: C / C++ / JAVA\n
&#8226;Winning Criteria: Only two winners will be decided at the end of event
from all the languages combined. The winning criteria will be no. of
questions submitted (full/partial test case), in shortest time. The
evaluation will be postponed till final code check.\n
&#8226;Note: Results will be solely decided by the jury members, and will be
final and declarative in all cases.\n </item>
       <item>&#8226; There should not be any change in the core logic of the problem
or else it will be considered wrong.\n
&#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those
having less points but completed in less time\n
&#8226; Partially submitted test cases will be counted and checked after
the contest again for verification.\n
&#8226; Partially Submitted test cases have points equivalent to number
of test cases passed.\n
&#8226; Usage of mobile phones and Internet is prohibited; any
participant found indulging in any such activity will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; Indulgence in any indisciplinary activity or usage of unfair means
will lead to cancellation of candidature.\n
&#8226; If two teams have same points then completion time will be
considered as tie breaker.\n
&#8226; Any team has to explain his logic and approach for a particular
question if any doubt is raised.\n
&#8226; Number of wrong attempts are counted and will be used for tie
breaker.\n
       </item>
        <item>15 October\n
        3:00PM to 5:00Pm</item>
        <item>A-Block Basement Lab 1 - Lab 8 and LT 1-4</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sakshi Vishnoi - 9650739480</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="cs_6">
    <item>Language Quiz\n
        Test Potential
    </item>
    <item>
        &#8226;No. Of Rounds: 1\n
        &#8226;Type: Individual as well as Team Event.\n
        &#8226;Description: This will be an event to test the general understanding of
        students for various programming paradigms, and language basics.
        However it will include a few tricky questions for shortlisting purpose.
        The programming languages to be tested will be C/C++/JAVA (Any One).
        There will be multiple choice questions.\n
        &#8226;Round 1:\n
        &#8226;Type: Quiz based on C/C++/JAVA\n
        &#8226;Time Limit: 1:30 hr.\n
        &#8226;Winning Criteria: Only two winners will be decided at the end of event
        from all the languages combined.\n
    </item>
    <item>&#8226; Participants having more points will be given priority over those
        having less points but completed in less time\n
        &#8226; Use of Internet is prohibited; any participant found indulging in
        any such activity will be disqualified.\n
        &#8226; Indulgence in any indisciplinary activity or usage of unfair means
        will lead to cancellation of candidature.\n
        &#8226; If two teams have same points then number of wrong answers
        will be considered as tie breaker.\n
    </item>
    <item>17 October\n
        2:00PM to 4:00 PM
    </item>
        <item>A-Block Basement Lab 1 - Lab 8 and LT 1-4</item>
        <item>&#8226;Chirag Gupta - 7042104283</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cs_7">
        <item>Drishti</item>
       <item>
    Objective:\n
Build an autonomous robot that can traverse an arena cluttered with
colored shapes. The robot will process live video feed from an overhead
camera to make decisions.\n
Hardware Specification:\n
1. Dimension of robot should not exceed 15 cm x 15 cm.\n
2. Robot should be autonomous.\n
3. Robot should navigate using image processing.\n
4. No other sensor module will be allowed other than camera to sense
the arena.\n
5. Camera will be located on top of the arena provided by the
organizer.\n
6. Camera feed will be provided via USB 2.0.\n
7. Camera used in this event is Logitech 310 webcam (will be provided
by the organizers).\n
8. Robot should not damage the arena or leave any visible mark behind,
failing which the team may be disqualified.\n
Arena specification and points:\n
1. Arena is printed on flex of dimension 160 cm x 220 cm.\n
2. The robot should start from the green square and should reach the
red square covering blue squares and avoiding all other shapes and
colors.\n
3. For each blue square touched the robot will gain 15 points.\n
4. For each blue triangle touched the robot will loose 15 points.\n
5. For each blue circle touched the robot will loose 10 points.\n
6. By touching the small blue triangle the robot will neither loose nor
gain any point.\n
7. By reaching the red square (destination) the robot will get 25 points.\n
8. Background of arena is white.\n
Wining criteria:\n
Final ranking of the teams will be decided by the scores obtained by the
team. In case of more than one team scoring equal points the team
clocking lesser time will be ranked higher.\n
       </item>
        <item>1. Competitors have to use their own laptop for image processing.\n
2. Teams must use the live feed from an overhead camera, provided by
the organizers.\n
3. Each team will be given two runs. Best of the two performances will
be taken as final performance by the team.\n
4. Lego and other ready-made kits are not allowed.\n
5. Control signal to your robot may be wired or wireless (preferably
wireless).\n
6. 5 minutes will be given to each team for setting up their robot and
for test drive. After the event has started no team member will be
allowed to touch their laptop or robot.\n
7. Organizers have all rights to disqualify any team at any given time if
they found to be taking recourse to any foul practice.\n
8. Organizers have the right to inspect the program or adopt any other
mechanism to make sure that the robot is not making use of hard
coded path coordinates.\n
9. In case of any dispute decision of judges will be final.\n
10. It is to be noted that multiple runs by various robots may tarnish
the arena. The teams should make their code robust enough to take
care of this eventuality.\n
11. Each team will be given a maximum of 20 minutes to complete both
the runs.\n </item>
        <item>ALL THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Kalpana Chawla Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Nayna Gupta\n
        &#8226;Natya Gupta\n
        &#8226;Vaishali Tayal\n
        &#8226;Chinmay\n
        &#8226;Apoorv Parashar - 9560637538</item>

    </string-array>


    <!--Literary  ......................................-->

    <string name="about_literary">this is description about LITERARY.</string>
    <string-array name="literary_1">
        <item>English Debate</item>
        <item>
This will be a team contest, with each team consisting of 2 members. However, more than one team from each college can register for the event.
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226; One member from each team will speak for the motion and the other will speak against the motion.\n
&#8226; Each speaker will present his/her speech in English and then answer,in English only, one question from the audience. The speaker will be
judged on the following criteria, and will be awarded marks
accordingly.\n
&#8226; Interpretation of the Motion.\n
&#8226; Logical Presentation of Argument.\n
&#8226; Evidences and Examples\n
&#8226; Audibility and Loudness\n
&#8226; Stance and Gestures\n
&#8226; Address and Format\n
&#8226; Elocution / Diction / Fluency\n
&#8226; Rebuttal of Interjection\n
&#8226; Time limit- The speaker will speak for 3 minutes. A warning bell will
be rung after 21⁄2 minutes, and a final bell will be rung after the third
minute. Exceeding the prescribed time, negative marks will be
awarded.
        </item>
        <item>15 October\n
            3:00PM to 5:00PM</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 1 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Nupur Tripathi\n
              &#8226;Sanjeev Kumar Saini</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literary_2">
        <item>Hindi Debate</item>
        <item>
This will be a team contest, with each team consisting of 2 members. However, more than one team from each college can register for the event. </item>
        <item>
  &#8226; This will be a team contest, with each team consisting of 2 members.
However, more than one team from each college can register for the
event.\n
&#8226; One member from each team will speak for the motion and the other
will speak against the motion.\n
&#8226; Each speaker will present his/her speech in Hindi and then answer, in
Hindi only, one question from the audience. The speaker will be judged
on the following criteria, and will be awarded marks accordingly.\n
&#8226; Interpretation of the Motion\n
&#8226; Logical Presentation of Argument\n
&#8226; Evidences and Examples\n
&#8226; Audibility and Loudness\n
&#8226; Stance and Gestures\n
&#8226; Address and Format\n
&#8226; Elocution / Diction / Fluency\n
&#8226; Rebuttal of Interjection\n
&#8226; Time limit- The speaker will speak for 3 minutes. A warning bell will be
rung after 21⁄2 minutes, and a final bell will be rung after the third
minute. Exceeding the prescribed time, negative marks will be awarded\n
        </item>
        <item>16 October
            \n10:00AM to 12:00PM</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 1 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Alok Gupta\n
            &#8226;Priya Gupta</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literary_3">
        <item>Crucible Quiz</item>
        <item> &#8226;Description:will be updated soon
        </item>


<item>General Rules:\n
&#8226; Only team entries are eligible.\n
&#8226; A team shall consist of two persons.\n
&#8226; The participants shall not be allowed to use mobile or other
electronic instruments.\n
&#8226; The questions shall be in the form of multiple choice, True / False
statement, Specific-answer question etc.\n
&#8226; The decision of the quiz-master will be final and will not be
subjected to any change.\n
This quiz will be held in 2 rounds.\n
-Elimination Round\n
-Stage Round\n
Elimination Round:\n
&#8226; Each team would be given 30 questions each to answer.\n
&#8226; Time limit - 15 minutes.\n
&#8226; Only 6 Teams would be selected for STAGE ROUNDS.\n
&#8226; In case of tie between 2 or more teams, further 3 questions would
be asked for final selectionStage Rounds\n
First Round:\n
&#8226; Each team would be asked 2 questions.\n
&#8226; 10 marks for correct answer, and no negative marking for wrong
answer.\n
&#8226; Answering time is only 30 seconds.
Second Round\n
&#8226; This Round would be the Buzzer Round.\n
&#8226; 10 marks for the correct answer and negative 5 marks for the wrong or
no answer if team Buzzers.\n
&#8226; Answering time is only 30 seconds\n
Third Round:\n
&#8226; This Round would be the Audio-visual round.\n
&#8226; 10 marks for the correct answer and negative 5 marks for the wrong
answer\n
&#8226; Each Team would be asked 2 audio-visual questions.\n
&#8226; Answering time is only 15 seconds.\n
Fourth Round:\n
&#8226; This round is a rapid fire round.\n
&#8226; 3 marks for the correct answer and negative 2 marks for the wrong
answer\n
&#8226; Each team would be asked 10 questions each which they have to
answer in minimum time frame.\n
        </item>
        <item>15 October
            \n11:00AM to 1:00PM
        </item>
        <item>Auditorium Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Manish Singh</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literary_4">
        <item>SRT</item>
        <item> &#8226;Description:will be updated soon
        </item>


<item>
    &#8226; The event is an individual event.\n
&#8226; Each participant will be given a situation and they are to react on it.\n
&#8226; The participants would be judged on the following criteria.\n
&#8226; Immediate reaction\n
&#8226; Logical Presentation\n
&#8226; Examples\n
&#8226; Audibility and Loudness\n
&#8226; Expression and Gestures\n
&#8226; Diction / Fluency\n
&#8226; Time limit- The speaker will speak for 3 minutes. A warning bell\n
will be rung after 21⁄2 minutes, and a final bell will be rung after\n
the third minute. Exceeding the prescribed time, negative marks
will be awarded.  </item>
        <item>17 October\n1:00PM to 3:00PM </item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 2 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Prashant Kumar\n &#8226;Ayush Jain</item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literary_5">
        <item>Poetry</item>
        <item>&#8226; Description:will be updated soon
        </item>


<item>&#8226; This is an individual contest.\n
&#8226; Participants are to recite a poem either in Hindi or English.\n
&#8226; Extra marks would be awarded to self-composed poetry.\n
&#8226; The participants will be judged on the following criteria, and will be
awarded marks accordingly.\n
&#8226; Presentation\n
&#8226; Audibility and Clarity\n
&#8226; Stance and Gestures\n
&#8226; Diction / Fluency\n
&#8226; Time limit- The participant would be given 3 minutes to recite. A
warning bell will be rung after 21⁄2 minutes, and a final bell will be
rung after the fifth minute. Exceeding the prescribed time, negative
marks will be awarded. </item>
        <item>17 October\n
        10:00AM to 12:00PM</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 2 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Aaquib Faridi</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="literary_6">
        <item>Triathlon</item>
        <item>&#8226; Rounds:\n
&#8226; Technical Quiz\n
&#8226; Talent Show\n
&#8226; Extempore\n
        </item>


<item>
General Rules\n
&#8226; The event is an individual event, where each participant will have to pass
through 3 rounds.\n
&#8226; The participant can move on to the next stage of the event as soon as he
finishes the prior one.\n
&#8226; Each participant will be scored separately for each round and then a
cumulative score would decide the winner.\n
&#8226; In case of a tie, a tie breaker round will be introduced.\n
&#8226; In case of ambiguity, the decision of the event head would be final.\n
&#8226; Technical Quiz\n
&#8226; The quiz shall consist of 45 technical questions based on simple maths,
physics, chemistry and general knowledge.\n
&#8226; The participants will get limited time to solve the quiz.\n
&#8226; Participants shall not be allowed to use mobile or other electronic
instruments.
    \n&#8226; Talent \n
&#8226; In this round each participant has to entertain the judges for at least 3
mins (max 4 mins).\n
&#8226; A participant can showcase any of his/her talent such as acting, mimicry,
mono act, dance, singing, poetry recitation or any other talent.\n
&#8226; Participants can use props, costumes, makeup, instruments etc. which
will not be provided by the organisers.\n
&#8226; All participants who wish to showcase their dancing or singing skills,
should positively hand over their music/karaoke to the organiser before
the commencement of the event.\n
&#8226; Extempore\n
&#8226; The final stage of the event would be an Extempore.\n
&#8226; Each participant will be provided 2mins to prepare for his/her topic.
The topic would be provided there hand.\n
&#8226; Each participant will have to speak for at least 2 mins to qualify.\n
&#8226; Participants would be judged on the following criteria\n
&#8226; Interpretation of the Topic\n
&#8226; Logical Presentation\n
&#8226; Audibility and Loudness\n
&#8226; Stance and Gestures\n
&#8226; Elocution / Diction / Fluency\n
&#8226;
Time limit- The speaker will speak for 3 minutes. A warning bell will
be rung after 21⁄2 minutes, and a final bell will be rung after the third
minute. Exceeding the prescribed time of 3 minutes, negative marks
will be awarded </item>
        <item>16 October\n
            12:00PM to 3:00PM</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 1,2,3 Raman Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Pawnesh Mishra</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- Tech civil  ......................................................................-->
    <string name="about_ce">this is description about civil.</string>
    <string-array name="ce_1">
        <item>Bob The Builder</item>
        <item>
In this event we call aspiring engineers to innovate , apply concepts and substantiate the bridge of their dreams. Make bridge using ice-cream sticks and fevicol.The load bearing capacity and stabiltiy of bridges will be checked </item>
   <item>
   &#8226; Maximum 4 participants per team .\n
&#8226; Switching team will lead to disqualification of both
the teams.\n
&#8226; Adherence of time and deadline are a must\n
&#8226; Event organizers reserve the right to make any
changes to the event as/when deemed necessary\n
&#8226; The decisions made by the judges will be final\n
&#8226; Materials provided must be dealt with care and few
may be subjected to return.\n
&#8226; Design specification during fabrication and buildingmust be adhered to.\n
&#8226; Any form of misbehavior may account to
disqualification of the team.\n
&#8226; Minimum length of span =50cm.\n
&#8226; Minimum height of truss =2 stick.\n
&#8226; No. of sticks =60.\n
&#8226; Fevicol will be provided as binder.\n
&#8226; 2 hours for fabrication and construction\n
&#8226; Next day testing #weight balance.


   </item>
        <item>&#8226;15 October\n
        10:00AM to 2:00PM
        \n &#8226;FINAL\n
        &#8226;16 October\n
        12:00PM to 1:00PM</item>
        <item>Civil Lab Ramanujam Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sumit Kumar Rai -  987326265\n &#8226;Ravi Verma - 9560020967</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ce_2">
        <item>Beat-D-Euclid</item>
        <item> &#8226;Description\n
         You can not do it unless you imagine it\n

On the Spot Event which test the perception and modelling abilties of the participants. It is a 2-d visualization of a given 3-d Structure in a given timespan using auto-cad software

        </item>

   <item>Rules:\n
       &#8226; Try to make the drawing resemble as close as
possible to original structure\n
&#8226; The drawing must be done in given amount of time\n
&#8226; Make appropriate judgment of dimension for every
part of the building\n
&#8226; Other figures (like trees etc)present in the
surrounding is not required\n
&#8226; No internet is allowed\n
&#8226;Event organizers reserve the right to make any
changes to the event as/when deemed necessary\n
&#8226;The decision made by the judges will be final\n
&#8226; Any form of misbehavior may account to disqualify
the person

   </item>
        <item>16 October\n
        10:00am to 12:00 pm
        </item>
        <item>AutoCad Lab Ramanujam Ground Floor</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sanjay Manohar - 9990039686\n &#8226;Nirali - 9873304121</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ce_3">
        <item>Archipedia(Presentation)</item>
        <item>
In this we introduce a kind assesment and presentation of our historical monuments that how they are still standing and are so stable and how long will they survive and are they in need of serious maintenance.
   </item>

   <item>
       &#8226; The event is open to all.\n
       &#8226; The maximum team size is two.\n
&#8226; The participants will have to submit an abstract .\n
&#8226; Relevant statistics and data can be added as
appendices at the end.\n
&#8226; All submissions must be done before 1 week of
genero.\n
&#8226; Selected teams will have to present their ideas (in the
form of PowerPoint Presentation) during GENERO
2015 in ABES ENGINEERING COLLEGE.\n
&#8226; The decision of the judges shall be final and binding.\n
&#8226; Any form of misbehavior may account to
disqualification of the team.\n

   </item>
        <item>16 October\n
            1:00pm to 3:00pm</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall-1 B-Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sarthak Garg - 8826950894\n &#8226;Nikhil - 8287203988</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ce_4">
        <item>Exhibition</item>
        <item>

The models are useful for demonstration of basic engineering concepts such as flow of force, tension and compression. It illustrates different kind of materials and various styles of architecture used in civil engineering.It is been introduced first time in Genero\'15 so, Be a Creator!!! A real engineer !!!Prepare a model and bring it for exhibiton
 </item>

   <item>&#8226;PARTICIPANT- MAXIMUM 4 PARTICIPANTS PER TEAM\n
&#8226; The model should be handmade with household and
stationary tools.\n
&#8226; Ready-made or factory made model will not be
accepted.\n
&#8226; Each group should present the list of materials used for
making the model, workability and functionality of the
model (through hard or soft copy at the time of the
exhibition).\n
&#8226; There will be a query session at the end of the
presentation by judges.\n
&#8226; Maximum team size should not exceed four members.\n
&#8226; Decision made by the judges will be final.\n

   </item>
        <item>17 october\n
        2:00pm to 4:00pm</item>
        <item>Ramanujam, Ground Floor</item>
        <item>&#8226;Kamlendra - 7827070467\n &#8226;Pulkit Vats - 8004696191</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ce_5">
        <item>CARTES DE PALAIS</item>
        <item>
            This event is to check the imagination of the participants and their insight into the field of architecture and design .Here the participants have to make the civil structure with help of 52 playing cards
</item>


   <item>&#8226; Maximum 2 members are allowed per team\n
        &#8226; Adherence of time and deadlines are a must\n
        &#8226; Event organizers reserve the rights to make any
        changes to the event.\n
        &#8226; The decision made by the judges will be final.\n
        &#8226; Material provided must be dealt with care and are
        subjected to return.\n
        &#8226; Use of any form of adhesives leads to disqualification
        of the team.\n
        &#8226; Any form of misbehavior may account to
        disqualification of the team.\n
   </item>
        <item>15 October\n
        2:00PM to 4:00PM</item>
        <item>Civil Lab Ramanujam</item>
        <item>&#8226;Khusbhoo Rani - 9716429443\n &#8226;Nitin Sharma - 9810376044</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ce_6">
        <item>Terramind</item>
        <item>
             It is a civil engineering quiz event testing the knowledge of participants in a wide range of fields namely environmental engineering, geo-technical, structure and various subject of civil department

\nOn The Spot Event
</item>
   <item>
        &#8226; Rules will be instructed one the spot
   </item>
        <item>17 October\n
        10:00am to 12:00pm</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall-1 B-Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vibha Palival - 8882179912\n &#8226;Shubham Kumar - 828795012</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- informals.................................................................... -->
    <string name="about_informals">this is description about INFORMALS.</string>
    <string-array name="informals_1">
        <item>Treasure Hunt</item>
        <item>
        It’s a hunt to find out the hidden articles, locations or places by using a series of clues. Each player will act upon successive clues and are eventually directed to a prize
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226; 3-4 Member in a team.\n
&#8226; 5 clues.\n
&#8226; 3 wrong guesses , team will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; Clues are In 200 yards of given area.
        </item>
        <item>15 October\n
       &#8226; 1st Round \n
        2:00pm to 4:00pm\n 16 October
        \n &#8226;FINAL\n
        12:00pm to 3:00pm
        </item>
        <item>Bhabha Block, Ramanujam Block,Stationery</item>
        <item>&#8226;Uphaar Darbari - 8860982449\n &#8226;Amber Agarwal - 9873685699</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_2">
        <item>Roadies</item>
        <item>
            &#8226;Roadies is a Youth Based Game
      </item>
        <item>
     &#8226;auditions(GD and PI) of the participants and some qualification(may be physical) tasks.\n
&#8226;physical tasks will be held on the day 2.
        </item>
        <item>&#8226;1st Round \n 16 October\n2:00pm-3:00pm
        \n &#8226;Final \n 17 October
            11:00am-1:00pm
        </item>
        <item>A-Block LT-6 for Round-1 and Front lawn for Round-2</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shubham Bisht - 9585224341\n &#8226;Vashuda Sharma - \n &#8226;Shubham Gautam - 8376905234</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_3">
        <item>Tug of War</item>
        <item>
      &#8226;A contest in which two teams pull against each other at opposite ends of a rope with the object of pulling the middle of the rope over a mark on the ground.
      </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; 8-10 members are allowed in one team.\n
&#8226; REFREE decisions will be final.
         </item>
        <item>15-17 October\n
        FULL DAY.</item>
        <item>Front Lawn</item>
        <item>&#8226;Suresh Pal - 8802912061\n &#8226;Swati Rai - 9711939919</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_4">
        <item>Face Painting</item>
        <item>
     &#8226;There will be a team of 2. One member will paint on another’s face and present something according to theme in order to win and explain your idea to judges. You have to bring your own colors

      </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; Only one person will paint.\n
&#8226; You cannot bring any photograph.\n
&#8226; You should bring your own colours.\n
&#8226; Time limit- 1hour
         </item>
        <item>15 October \n 1:00pm to 4:00pm</item>
        <item>Nescafe Front Lawn</item>
        <item>&#8226;Pooja Yadav - 9560958809\n &#8226;Vernica Raghav - 9873685548\n &#8226;Pranjal Pratap - 7838164861</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_5">
        <item>Rangoli</item>
        <item>
     &#8226;Rangoli is a folk art from India in which patterns are created on the floor in living rooms or courtyards
using materials such as coloured rice, dry flour, coloured sand or flower petals.
      </item>
        <item>
            &#8226;2-4 members team.\n
&#8226;Don’t bring design on paper and mobile .\n
&#8226;Colours will not be provided by organisers .\n
&#8226; Time limit will be 2 hours.
         </item>
        <item>16 October\n
        3:00pm -5:00pm</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block, Ground Floor </item>
        <item>&#8226;Poorva Goel - 9458579430\n &#8226;Shashank Gupta - 9811500270</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_7">
        <item>Dart Game</item>
        <item>
     &#8226;Darts is a form of throwing sport in which small missiles are thrown at a circular target (dartboard) fixed to a wall. The dart board is hung so that the center of the bulls eye is 5 ft 8in (1.73 m) from the floor. This is considered eye-level for a six-foot man.
      </item>
        <item>
            &#8226; 6 member can participate at one time.\n
&#8226; Closet target hitter or member with maximum points will win.\n
&#8226; Only 3 chances will be given to each member.
         </item>
        <item>16-17 October\n
        FULL DAY.</item>
        <item>Front Lawn</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sumit Pal - 9560628301\n &#8226;Sheetal Yadav - 8587980869</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="informals_6">
        <item>skectching</item>
        <item>&#8226;Description:\n will be updated soon.

      </item>
        <item>Rules
            &#8226;1 Member is allowed.\n
&#8226;Only sheets will be provided by the organisers.\n
&#8226;Time limit will be 1.5 hour.\n
         </item>
        <item>15 October\n
        11:00am to 2:00am</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block,Ground Floor</item>
        <item>&#8226;Pragya Mishra - 8800210724\n &#8226;Nayna Khokhar - 9643639949</item>

    </string-array>


    <!-- tech ec ............................................................................................. -->
    <string name="about_ec">this is description about EC.</string>
    <string-array name="ec_1">
        <item>Aquiziam\n
Every Thing Mysterious   </item>
        <item>
             &#8226;This is a event which requires a participant to reveal the
concent involved in a mythology based on ELECTRICAL and ELECTRONICS deptt.
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; Each participant has to explain the related mystery.\n
    &#8226; Mystery (topic) will be given on the spot.\n
    &#8226; Total 10 minutes is given to review the topic. You can use the google or any source\n
    &#8226; The best explanation will be declared as a winner.\n
    &#8226; If any application mentioned will counted as a plus point.\n
</item>
        <item>17 October\n 12:00pm to 2:00pm</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall-1 B-Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Manish Singh - 9414287741\n &#8226;Shreyansh Singh - 8826928095\n &#8226;Shashank Mani Rai - 8882887141</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ec_2">
        <item>RoboSoccer </item>
        <item>

&#8226;Real soccer will be implemented on small scale with two
teams, only difference is that each team will present a robot to play soccer.
        </item>
        <item>Rules-\n
        &#8226; 2 robots (each from different team) will play a game.\n
    &#8226; The robot must fit inside a square of size 30cm X 30cm\n
    &#8226; The robot must fit inside a square of size 30cm X 30cm\n
   &#8226;  Height of 20cms or less\n
   &#8226;  Weight approx 5000gms.(5 KG)\n
    &#8226; Robot wheels (or other surface that contact the playing surface) must be made of a Material that does not harm the playing surface.
    \n&#8226; A robot must not damage the opponent or else it will be disqualified.
    \n&#8226; A robot must not have in its construction anything that is dangerous to other robot If found, the team will be directly disqualified.
    \n&#8226; If the bot is controlled wirelessly, the bot must at least have a four frequency remote control Circuit or two dual control circuits which may be interchanged before the start of the race to avoid frequency interference with other teams.
   \n&#8226; The case of any interference in the wireless systems will not be considered for rematch or results.
    \n&#8226; The robots can drag or kick the ball. No other means are allowed (eg. Holding a ball).
        </item>
        <item> 16 October\n 11:00am-2:00pm</item>
        <item>Infront Of Sir John</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vishal Singh - 9651776020\n &#8226;Vakesh Singh - 8130670079\n &#8226;Shumaela Noor - 9910655019</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ec_3">
        <item>Line Follower </item>
        <item>
&#8226;A Micro Controller based robot will be designed to follow a
black line, the team’s whose robot will complete this in minimum time will be
winners.
        </item>
        <item>
    &#8226; Each team must comprise a maximum of 3 members . Each student must have a valid Id-Card of their college.
    \n&#8226;The bots will be put on the start mark and after that it should be automatic unless it reaches the end point.
    \n&#8226; If the bots deviates from the path then the bot will be put their again and sometime penalty will be awarded
    \n&#8226; For passing every check point 10 points will be awarded.
    \n&#8226; The whole event will consist of two rounds.\n
            PRELIMS-\n
&#8226; the first round is just following a simple path mixed with complex one(only black line).\n
&#8226; Width of the line would be 3cm.\n
&#8226; Those who reach the finish line will qualify for the finals.\n
&#8226; In case no one reaches the finish line fastest will be the qualifiers.\n
            FINALS-\n
&#8226; The final round comes with twist and turns.\n
&#8226; Width of the line would be 3cm.\n
&#8226; Team reaching the finish line in minimum time will win.\n
&#8226; Decision of the judges will be final. All power lies with the organizers to amend any rule if necessary.\n
</item>
        <item>15 October\n2:00pm-5:00pm</item>
        <item>Bhabha Block,Electronics Lab</item>
        <item>&#8226;Nitesh - 9717077012\n &#8226;Lalit Pawan - 7376061601</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ec_4">
        <item>RoboRace </item>
        <item>
&#8226;A robot will be designed which should be able to traverse a
path full of complications and challenges, team doing this in minimum time will
be declared as winners.
        </item>
        <item>
    \n&#8226; Maximum number of participants allowed per team is 4. Each student must have a valid Id-Card of their college.
    \n&#8226; Teams start their vehicles at starting line, on a signal given by the event coordinators. The timing will begin as soon as the signal is given.
    \n&#8226; Your vehicle should always remain inside the track. If your vehicle leaves the track, at any point of time, it gets penalized.
    \n&#8226; A vehicle remaining stationary for more than 45 seconds gets disqualified.
    \n&#8226; The coordinators hold the direction to restart a race, in case of a valid reason to do so.
    \n&#8226; Decision of the judges will be final. All power lies with the organizers to amend any rule if necessary.

</item>
        <item>17 October \n
            10:00am-4:00pm</item>
        <item>Beside Sir John</item>
        <item>&#8226;Siddharth Shukla - 9958443307\n &#8226;Rahul Agarwal - 8882568209\n &#8226;Shaswat Singh - 8377811601\n &#8226;gaurav - 8527656864</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ec_5">
        <item>RoboWar </item>
        <item>
&#8226;A heavy robot should be designed loaded with lethal weapons
in it’s own kind, the robot should be able to completely dismantle the opponent
robot.

        </item>
        <item>

   \n&#8226; The teams need to register in the group of four(max).
    \n&#8226; The maximum duration of each round will be 5 minutes. Any team that is not ready at the time specified will be disqualified.
   \n&#8226; The name of your machine must be prominently displayed on the machine.
   \n&#8226; Immobility (if robot is unable to travel at least 10 cm for 15 seconds) would lead to disqualification.
    \n&#8226; The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit. Change in rules, if any will be highlighted on the website and notified to the registered teams.
    \n&#8226; Violation of any of the above rules will lead to disqualification.
        </item>
        <item>15 October\n10:00am-2:00pm</item>
        <item>Infront Of Sir John</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vaibhav - 9953413033\n &#8226;Anurag - 9716931439</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ec_6">
        <item>MicroController </item>
        <item>
&#8226;This competition is based on the application of micro controller,
a task will be given and that task should be solved along with its simulation on
proteus.

        </item>
        <item>

   \n&#8226;  Each team must comprise a maximum of 2 members (not more than 2 persons are allowed).
    \n&#8226; Decision of the judges will be final. All power lies with the organizers to amend any rule if necessary.

</item>
        <item>15 October\n 11:00AM to 1:00PM</item>
        <item>Bhabha Block, Electronics Lab</item>
        <item>&#8226;Mayank - 9599585169\n &#8226;Sakshi - 9716140713</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ec_7">
        <item>Edge Follower </item>
        <item>

A micro controller based robot will be designed
which should be able to traverse an edge which could be in any shape.
        </item>
        <item>
   &#8226; Maximum 3 members are allowed in a team.
  \n&#8226;  Edge of the table can be of any shape and size at an elevation.
    \n&#8226; The bot should follow the provided edge of the table only.
    \n&#8226; Your vehicle should always follow the edge. If your vehicle leaves the edge, at any point of time, it gets penalized
   \n&#8226;  The best timing is declare as winner.
   \n&#8226;  The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit. Change in rules, if any will be highlighted on the website and notified to the registered teams.
</item>
        <item> 16 October\n
        2:00pm-5:00pm</item>
        <item>Bhabha Block Electronics Lab</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vedant Mishra - 7042349477\n &#8226;Saurav Goswami</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ec_8">
        <item>Real Time NFS </item>
        <item>

&#8226;Each participant will be given a robot to perform in a race along with other two participants. Participant which completes the
race in minimum time will be awarded instantly.

        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226; Registration will be done at venue of game.\n
&#8226; Only single player is allowed to play at a time(no team).\n
&#8226; Remote control bot is provided to play the game.\n
&#8226; A robot must not damage the opponent and arena or else it will be disqualified. Best
timing is declared as winner.\n
&#8226; The organizers reserve the rights to change any or all of the above rules as they deem fit.
Change in rules, if any will be highlighted on the website and notified to the registered teams.</item>
        <item>All Three Days</item>
        <item>Infront Vishwakarma</item>
        <item>&#8226;Suyash Tiwari\n &#8226;Sakshi Sharma\n &#8226;Vivek Yadav\n &#8226;Surendra - 9555218310</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ec_9">
        <item>Circuit Designing </item>
        <item>

&#8226;Each team will design a circuit based on any application .
Best working circuit will be declared as winner.

        </item>
        <item>
&#8226; Each team must comprise a maximum of 2 members (not more than 2 persons are allowed).\n
&#8226; Decision of the judges will be final. All power lies with the organizers to amend any rule if necessary.\n
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n 10:00AM to 2:00PM</item>
        <item>Bhabha Block, Electronics Lab</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vinod Kr. Gupta - 9873272860\n &#8226;Bharti - 9540669147\n &#8226;Yadu singh - 9910540962</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ec_10">
        <item>Maze Solving</item>
        <item>
&#8226;It is a line following type maze solving event in which the robot is required to traverse the whole arena
and reach the end point in minimum time. The complete task is divided into two parts which are as
follows:\n
&#8226; Completely traverse the arena and create a virtual map of the arena (maze mapping).\n
&#8226; Once the map has been created, find the feasible path from the map and traverse it (maze
traversal).\n
            \nHardware Specification:\n
&#8226; Dimension of robot should not be more than 15 cm x 15 cm.\n
&#8226; Robot should be autonomous.\n
&#8226; Robot should not damage the arena or leave any visible mark behind, failing which the team
may be disqualified.\n
            \nArena Specification and Points:\n
&#8226; Width of the black line is 3 cm.\n
&#8226; Size of complete arena is 160 cm x 220 cm.\n
&#8226; During maze mapping round 5 points will be rewarded for successful crossing of each junction.
It is to be noted that there are 12 junctions (please see the attached image).\n
&#8226; During maze traversal round 10 points will be rewarded for successful crossing of each junction
that is part of the feasible path. It is to be noted that the feasible path consists of 6 junctions
(please see the attached image).\n
&#8226; During maze mapping round teams are allowed to manually assist the robot to maintain course.
But only one person from each team is allowed to touch the robot. A maximum of 3 such
touching is allowed and with each such touch the team has to forfeit 10 points.\n
&#8226; During the maze traversal round teams are not allowed to touch their robot.\n
\nWining criteria:\n
&#8226;Final ranking of the teams will be decided by the scores obtained by the team. In case of more than one
team scoring equal points the team clocking lesser during the maze traversal round time will be ranked
higher.\n
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226; Robot should be autonomous.\n
&#8226; 5 minutes will be given to each team for setting up their robot and for test drive. After the
event has started no team member will be allowed to touch their robot.\n
&#8226; Organizers have all rights to disqualify any team at any given time if they found to be taking
recourse to any foul practice.\n
&#8226; Organizers have the right to inspect the program or adopt any other mechanism to make sure
that the robot is not making use of hard coded path coordinates.\n
&#8226; In case of any dispute decision of judges will be final.\n
&#8226; It is to be noted that multiple runs by various robots may tarnish the arena. The teams should
make their code robust enough to take care of this eventuality.\n
&#8226; Each team will be given a maximum of 20 minutes to complete both the rounds.\n

        </item>
        <item>All three days</item>
        <item>Spark Lab</item>
        <item>&#8226;Umang Varshney\n &#8226;Akansha Guatam - 9910687188\n &#8226;Sanklap Dixit</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- Dramatics ..........................................................................................-->
    <string name="about_drama">this is description about DRAMITICS.</string>
    <string-array name="drama_1">
        <item>NUKKAD NATAK
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226;will be updated soon</item>
        <item> Rules:\n
        &#8226; The team shall consist of maximum of 14 people excluding 2 instrumentalists (optional).\n
&#8226; the time limit shall be 12 minutes\n
&#8226; In case of violation, participants will be penalized by judges. The given time duration is from empty stage to empty stage.\n
&#8226; Any instance of vulgarity or disturbing content of any order will lead to forceful halt of performance and immediate disqualification.\n
&#8226; Teams are expected to perform at an open air venue, on a circular stage with audience on all
sides.\n
&#8226; Only live music is allowed. Teams will have to bring their own instruments.\n
&#8226; Audience response will have substantial points in scoring criteria.\n
&#8226; Judging Criterion:\n
&#8226; 30 % - Content\n
&#8226; 25 % - Acting/ Expression\n
&#8226; 20 % - Audience Response\n
&#8226; 15 % - Direction\n
&#8226; 10 % - Miscellaneous Effects\n
&#8226; The judge\'s decision will be final and binding.\n
&#8226; The organizing team reserves the right to change or modify any of the rules.
        </item>
        <item>15 October\n 3:00pm to 5:00pm</item>
        <item>front lawn</item>
        <item>&#8226;Ojasva Bhardwaj - 8467966698\n &#8226;Kanika Dhyani - 9912102358</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="drama_2">
        <item>RANGMANCH
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226;will be updated soon</item>
        <item>
       &#8226; This is a group event. Each team should have a minimum of 10 actors. In addition there can be 1
person in charge of music and a maximum of 3 people for lights.\n
&#8226; Time allotted for the performance will be 20 minutes.. there ill be a negative marking on the
extent of time.\n
&#8226; Language of the play can be English/Hindi. Mime is allow\n
            &#8226; Teams should mail a soft copy of the script on our site..\n
&#8226; This is an inter-collegiate event and there shall be only 1 team per college. The teams should
carry an official letter from their respective institutes signed by a competent authority,
mentioning the names of the participants.\n
&#8226; Once a team registers, their preference for a slot for prelims and lights practice will be taken by
email. The organizing team shall try to give the preferential slot as long as it is available.\n
&#8226; The teams will be informed regarding their lights practice and prelims slots by email.\n
&#8226; Microphones and backstage mikes for narration, lights, and a laptop to play sounds will be
provided.\n
&#8226; Recorded vocals are allowed.\n
&#8226; The teams are expected to bring their own music on CD or pen drive for the play.\n
&#8226; In case of malfunctioning of any equipment provided, the team will be allowed to repeat their
performance from the last scene change or from the point of disruption that the team wishes. It
depends on the judge\'s discretion as to how much grace time will be given to the performing
team\n
&#8226; All costumes and accessories are to be arranged by the participating team. The organizing
committee is responsible for the infrastructural facilities only and shall not be responsible for the
security of items left behind in green rooms or on stage after the performance.\n
&#8226; Requests for special effects and props should be communicated at least a week in advance by
both email and over the telephone. The same will be provided only if possible.\n
&#8226; No naked flames or live animals are allowed on stage.\n
&#8226; The participating teams are requested to ensure that their presentation is in keeping with the
dignity of the fest.\n
&#8226; The judge\'s decision will be final and binding.\n
&#8226; The organizing team reserves the right to change or modify any of the decisions..
        </item>
        <item>17 October\n 11:00am to 3:00pm</item>
        <item>Auditorium</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shubham Gupta - 8742948778\n &#8226;Mohini Singh - 8860385179</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="drama_3">
        <item>MANMARZI
        </item>
        <item>  &#8226;Description :\n
        Manmarzi is the solo acting,duet acting, mime mimicry competition in genero. This event Is a
true strength of one\'s versatility and acting powers. Widely participated in by a large number of
promising actors, the event hosts various one-actor plays, ranging from the comic to the
poignant. When the curtain is lifted and the lights go on, can you step up to the stage and own it,
on your own?
        </item>
        <item> Rules:\n
       &#8226; This is an individual or duet event.\n
&#8226; There can be 1 person to assist with sounds and a maximum of 1 people to assist with lights.\n
&#8226; Language of the act can be English/Hindi\n
            &#8226; Total time allotted for every performance is 5 minutes (empty stage to empty stage).\n
&#8226; If a participant exceeds the stipulated time, 15% of the total marks obtained will be deducted. If
he/she exceeds 6 min, he/she stands to be debarred from the event.\n
&#8226; Microphones, lights and a laptop to play sounds will be provided.\n
&#8226; Participants are expected to bring their own music on CD or pen drive for the act.\n
&#8226; Recorded vocals are allowed.\n
&#8226; All clothes and accessories are to be arranged by the participants. The organizing committee is
responsible only for the infrastructural facilities only and shall not be responsible for the security
of items left behind in green rooms or stage.\n
&#8226; Naked flames or live animals are not allowed on stage.\n
&#8226; The participating teams are requested to ensure that their presentation is in keeping with the
dignity of the fest.\n
&#8226; The judge\'s decision will be final and binding..
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n 10:00am to 12:00pm</item>
        <item>Auditorium</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shivam Aggarwal - 9717937118\n &#8226;Radhika Chauhan - 9953214731</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="drama_4">
        <item>AD MAD SHOW
        </item>
        <item>
        &#8226;Bring out the creativity inside you and make an outstanding advertisement of your own. Be it hilarious
or sensitive, be it just your creativity and ad sense.
        </item>
        <item>
       &#8226; It is a team event. Each team should have 4-5 members only.\n
&#8226; Topics would be of the choice of participants.\n
&#8226; Time limit for the performing the advertisement is 2 minutes.\n
&#8226; Participants shall be judged on the basis of spontaneity, content, adherence to the topic, on-stage presentation,
 coordination and overall appeal of the advertisement.\n
&#8226; The caution should be taken to refrain from displaying obscenity, violence, prejudice, defamation etc. in
Advertisement.\n
&#8226; Decision of the judge\'s will be final and binding.
        </item>
        <item>15 October\n 10:00am to 2:00pm</item>
        <item>Auditorium</item>
        <item>&#8226;Saurabh Gautam- 9971021320\n &#8226;Maahi Rajpoot- 9818645570</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="drama_5">
        <item>YE KARKE DIKHA
        </item>
        <item>
     &#8226;will updated soon.
        </item>
        <item>
       &#8226; It is a team event max 4-5.\n
&#8226; Topic would be the choice of orgnisers.\n
&#8226; Each team would be given 11 minutes 5 min to prepare and next 5 min minutes to inact and 1 minute
for any set arrangement.\n
&#8226; Participants will be judges on the basis of spontaenity,content, adherence on the theme given,stage
presentation, coordination, and appeal of the act.\n
&#8226; No obscenity,violence,prejudice,defamation is allowed.\n
&#8226; decisions will be final and binding.
        </item>
        <item>16 October\n 3:00pm to 5:00pm</item>
        <item>Auditorium</item>
        <item>&#8226;Surendra Pratap - 9555208320\n &#8226;Sooraj Singh - 8010040660</item>

    </string-array>

    <!-- E-Gaming .........................................................................-->
    <string name="about_gaming">this is description about E-GAMING.</string>
    <string-array name="gaming_1">
        <item>CALL OF DUTY</item>
        <item>
&#8226; Team members : 3 vs. 3 (Team Play, 3 players per
team)\n
&#8226; Operation System: Windows 7/windows 8\n
&#8226; Victory Condition: The team which scores highest
points is declared as winner. (3rounds from semi
Finals onward )\n
&#8226; Semifinal/Final match will be “BEST OF THREE MAPS”\n
 Official Maps:/n
&#8226; CROSSFIRE\n
&#8226; BACKLOT\n
&#8226; BOG\n
&#8226; WET WORK\n
&#8226; SHOW DOWN\n
*There will be lucky draw to choose the map.\n
            General game setting :\n
&#8226;Round Time: 10 minutes.\n
&#8226;Voice chat will be enabled.\n
&#8226;Old school will be disabled.\n
&#8226;Friendly fire will be disabled.\n
&#8226;Kill cam will be enabled.\n
Instructions:\n
&#8226;Players can bring their own mouse, keyboard,
headphones.\n
&#8226; Players will play with default custom class (except in
semifinal/final)\n
&#8226; Players will be allowed to create their own custom
class in semifinal and final matches.\n
&#8226; Every team should have a team name.

        </item>
        <item>
       &#8226;     General rules:\n

&#8226; On the spot registration will be done only on 15th and 16th October.\n
&#8226; Online registration is also available on GENERO’14
website .Last day for online registration is 15th October\n
&#8226; All participants in a team must have valid
college/university/school Identity cards while
registration and when asked for.\n
&#8226; In case of any identity card related dispute
participant detail will be verified on university
website.\n
&#8226; It is a college level fest so, professional clans are
strictly not allowed.\n
&#8226; Player must respect the spirit of fair play and non-
violence.\n
&#8226; Use of personal map texture/model/skins (includes
weapon skins) is NOT permitted.\n
&#8226; In case of any dispute organizers decision will be
considered final.\n
&#8226; Third party program/additional softwares like mouse
fix and dll’s will not be allowed.\n
&#8226; If teams are not fulfilling the criteria of the rulesmentioned above,Then their registration will not be considered.\n
Unfair Practices Subject to Penalty\n

&#8226; Team members may communicate verbally if they are
alive in the match or when all team members are dead.\n
&#8226; Bugs are strictly not allowed .If bug is decided as
unintentional, the game continues as normal. If the use
of the bug is decided as intentional, the offending team
will be a given a warning /loss by default (depends on
organizers).\n
&#8226; God mode/cheats will be strictly probhited.\n
&#8226; HLTV Proxy will join the game servers for Tournament
Broadcast.\n
If disconnection occurs during a match\n
&#8226; If all the players cannot play due to an unintended,
unforeseen accident such as server stoppage,
Match will be restarted.\n
&#8226; If any one of all players are unintentionally
disconnected: The match is restart,irrespective ofwinning or loosing.
Rules for Tie-breaker\n
&#8226; In case of a tie another match will be played.
        </item>
        <item>ALL THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Ground Floor And Kalpana Chawla labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;Kanak Raj Verma - 9654017856\n &#8226;Priya Bansal - 9711707510 </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gaming_2">
        <item>CRICKET 07</item>
        <item>
        MATCH FORMAT:\n
&#8226; Exhibition match will be of 5-5 overs on RANDOM
pitch and weather type, MISCELLANEOUS location
having 5 STAR difficulty.\n
&#8226; Semifinals will be of 10-10 overs match.\n
&#8226; Final will be of 20-20 overs match.\n
        </item>

        <item>

RULES TO BE FOLLOWED:\n
&#8226; On the spot registration will be done on 15th October.\n
&#8226; Batsman decides whether to play with gamepad or
joystick.\n
&#8226; Headphones/earphones are allowed and players are
supposed to bring their own headphone.\n
&#8226;You are allowed to select only International team.
Australian/English, any other states cannot be
selected.\n
&#8226; If conflict occurs in selecting the teams then, coin
toss will decide the choice of the team.\n
&#8226; Participants are allowed to choose their own squad
but no custom player is allowed.\n
&#8226; Camera view will be default. But if both the
participants agree for any other camera (as per
choice), then camera view can be changed.\n
&#8226; Custom fielding option is not allowed. However, the
default fielding option can be set.\n
&#8226; No negative bowling (spinners are not allowed to
bowl on backside of the wicket)\n
&#8226;
In case of any conflict, organizer’s decision will be
final.
&#8226;
If anyone found cheating /disobeying the rules,
will be disqualified.
        </item>
        <item>All THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block Ground Floor and Kalpana Chawla Labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;Saurabh Agarwal - 9711962594\n &#8226;Kanika Agarwal - 7503244700</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gaming_3">
        <item>Counter Strike 1.6</item>
        <item>Description:\n
       &#8226;Clan members:\n
5 vs 5(Team Play, 5 players per team)\n
&#8226;Operating System:
Windows 8/Windows 7 \n
&#8226;Winning Condition:\n
The first team to win 11 rounds is declared the winner.
(16 rounds from Quarter Finals onwards)\n
&#8226;Official Maps:\n
de_dust2, de_inferno , de_nuke , de_train:\n
&#8226; There will be a toss to decide which map to play.
Winner eliminates 2 maps and the opponent
eliminates 1, remaining map shall be played. There
will be a knife round to decide the side (CT\T)\n
&#8226; The Server Master will/can record the demo of the
match (or on players demand).\n
            General Game Setting:\n
&#8226; There will be swap at 10 rounds first team to win 11
rounds will proceed to the next stage of the
tournament.\n
&#8226; Round Time: 1 minute 45 seconds.\n
&#8226; C4 Timer: 35 seconds.\n
&#8226; Players are expected to bring their gaming
accessories.(Keyboard , Mouse-optional)\n
&#8226; Final match will be “BEST OF THREE MAPS”.
Unfair Practises Subject to Penalty:\n
&#8226; Team members may communicate verbally if they
are alive in the match or when all team members are
dead\n
&#8226; The player is deemed dead when the screen is
completely faded to black.If a bug occurs and the
screen doesn’t fade to black,the player is deemed dead
three seconds after he/she has fallen. C4 must be installed at viewable location.
Installing C4 at a location where a boost is required is
allowed.\n
&#8226; Silent C4 installation is considered illegal. This
offence may result in a warning or loss of rounds.\n
&#8226; Bugs are strictly not allowed. If bug is decided as
unintentional, the game continues as normal. If the use
of bug is decided as intentional, the offending team will
be given a warning/loss by default (depend on
organizers).\n
&#8226; Gay gun (krieg 550 commando and D3/AU-1) and
shield are not allowed.Use of these weapon result in -1
round score for the offending team.\n
&#8226; Use of unfair but available scripts (e.g silentrun ,
attack+use,centerview script,norecoil script,etc.) will
have the offending team disqualified with no further
considerations.\n
&#8226; HLTV Proxy will join the game server for the
Tournament Broadcast.If disconnection occurs during a match:
If all the players cannot play due to an unintended,
unforeseen accident such as server stoppage will be
handled by server administrator as:\n
&#8226; Before the 3 rd round starts:
Match will be restarted.\n
&#8226; After the 3 rd round starts:
Disconnected player must re-connect to the server.
The round is continued unpausing,and if the disconnected
player cannot connect to the server,all players must wait during
the freeze time after the round until; the disconnected players
connects to server .At this time ,the match may continue by
unpausing .(Not a restart).\n
&#8226;If up to 3 of all players are unintentionally disconnected ,the
score for that round is discarded .The game is paused after the
round during freeze time ,and all players wait until disconnected
players are connected to the server. When all players are
connected, the match may continue by unpausing the game.In case of problems (disconnection of player, high latency,
problem with accessorised) if the server master is unable to
pause the server due to technical issues ,following rules shall be
considered.\n
&#8226; Problem within 3 rounds: Match restarts.
&#8226; Within 3-6 rounds :Match will be continued with start
money $4000.\n
&#8226; After 6 rounds :Match will be continued with start money
$8000.
        </item>
        <item>
        Rules for Tie-breaker:\n
        &#8226; In case of a tie after regulation rounds ends,6 rounds
        shall be played.3 rounds as Terrorists and 3 as
        Counter Terrorists.\n
        &#8226; Initial start money $10000.General rules:\n
        &#8226; On the spot registration will be done only on 15th and 16th October.\n
        &#8226; Online registration is also available on genero’15
        website .Last day for online registration is 15th October.\n
        &#8226; All participants in a team must have valid
        college/university/school identity cards while
        registration and when asked for.\n
        &#8226; In case of any identity card related dispute
        participant details will be verified on the university
        website.\n
        &#8226; It is a college level fest so , professional clans are
        strictly not allowed.\n
        &#8226; Players must respect the spirit of fair play and non-
        violence.\n
        &#8226; Clans can bring their CFG’s but should be in single
        PENDRIVE ,which will be checked before match starts
        . Any other data except CFG will be deleted.\n&#8226; Use of personal map texture/model/skins
        (includes
        weapon skins) is NOT permitted.\n
        &#8226; In case of any dispute organizers decision will be
        considered final.\n
        &#8226; Third party programme/additional software like
        mouse_fix and dll’s will not be allowed.\n
        &#8226; If teams are not fulfilling the criteria of the rules
        mentioned above, then their registration will not be
        considered.(Registration fees will not be refunded in
        any case).



        </item>
        <item>All THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block Ground Floor and Kalpana Chawla Labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shashank Verma\n &#8226;Krishna Kumar Varshney - 9818064941</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gaming_4">
        <item>FIFA</item>
        <item>&#8226;Description:\n
            will update soon.

        </item>
        <item>
        PRE-ROUNDS:\n
        &#8226; Half -length duration: 4min.\n
        &#8226; Bookings: ON.\n
        &#8226; Offside: ON.\n
        &#8226; Injuries: ON.\n
        QUARTERFINAL:\n
        &#8226; Half –length duration: 5min.\n
        &#8226; Bookings: ON.\n
        &#8226; Offside: ON.\n
        &#8226; Injuries: ON.\n
        SEMI-FINAL:\n
        &#8226; Half –length duration: 6min.\n
        &#8226; Bookings: ON.\n
        &#8226; Offside: ON.\n
        &#8226; Injuries: ON.FINAL:\n
        &#8226; Half –length duration: 7min.\n
        &#8226; Bookings: ON.\n
        &#8226; Offside: ON.\n
        &#8226; Injuries: ON.\n
        NOTE:\n
        &#8226; ON THE PLAY SPOT REGISTRATION WILL BE
        DONE ON 15th and 16th October.\n
        &#8226; PLAYERS CAN PLAY ONLY WITH KEYBOARD.\n
        &#8226; NO CUSTOMIZER TEAMS OR PLAYERS CAN BE
        USED IN GAME PLAY IN ANY ROUND.\n
        &#8226; GOALS SHOT DIRECTLY FROM CENTER WON’T BE
        COUNTED.\n
        &#8226; PLAYERS CANNOT SHOOT DIRECTLY AT GOAL
        FROM 4M CORNER.\n
        &#8226; EXTRA TIME(CLASSIC) IN CASE OF DRAW WOULD
        BE TAKEN FOR ALL ROUNDS FOLLOWED BY
        PENALTY SHOOTOUTS,WHILE IN CASE OF DRAW
        IN FINAL GOLDEN GOAL RULE WILL IMPLY. IN CASE OF SERVER CLASH:\n
        &#8226; IF THE CRASH OCCURS IN FIRST HALF,MATCH WILL
        BE RESTARTED.\n
        &#8226; IF CRASH OCCURS IN SECOND HALF,SECOND HALF
        WILL BE RESTARTED FROM THE SCORE OF HALFTIME.\n
        &#8226; IN CASE OF FINAL,MATCH WILL BE RESTARTED AT
        ANY POINTOF SERVER CLASH.IF CRASH OCCURS IN
        EXTRA TIME DURING FINAL,EXTRA TIME WILL BE
        RESTARTED.\n
        &#8226; NO PENALTY SHOOTOUTS WILL BE DONE IN
        CASE OF DRAW IN FINAL.\n
        &#8226; OPPONENTS CAN CHOOSE SAME TEAM WHILE
        COMPETING.
        </item>
        <item>All THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block Ground Floor and Kalpana Chawla Labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;Saksham Gupta - 7503072824\n &#8226;Ankur Rathore</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="gaming_5">
        <item>Need for Speed : Most Wanted 1.3</item>
        <item>
            &#8226;Competition Mode: min 2 players.\n
Game Type: Circuit/Sprint.\n
Qualification: for next round will be decided on the
basis of individual player’s timing. Players with the
best timing will qualify for the next round.\n


        </item>
        <item>

        General:\n
        &#8226; Competition Mode: min 2 players.\n
        &#8226; Game Type: Circuit/Sprint.\n
        &#8226; Qualification: for next round will be decided on the
        basis of individual player’s timing. Players with the
        best timing will qualify for the next round.\n
        Car Settings:\n
        &#8226; Upgrades are NOT allowed.\n
        (It includes visual,performance,etc.)
        &#8226; Junkman is NOT allowed.\n
        &#8226; Personal saved files are NOT allowed.\n
        Tracks:\n
        &#8226; RANDOM\n
        &#8226; Each track will be decided by the Genero’14 NFS
        organizing committee.Race Mode Options:\n
        &#8226; Circuit/Sprint\n
        &#8226; Track Direction: Forward\n
        &#8226; Laps: At the discretion of Genero’14 NFS organizing
        committee\n
        &#8226; N20: On\n
        &#8226; Collision Detection: Off\n
        &#8226; Performance Matching: On\n
        &#8226; Min. Num. Players:2/4\n
        Control Setting:\n
        &#8226; Game control settings will be decided by Genero’14
        organizing committee.\n
        Player Options:\n
        &#8226; Cars: Cars will be decided by Genero’14 NFS
        organizing committee.\n
        &#8226; Car Damage: Off\n
        &#8226; Rearview Mirror: Player’s own discretion.\n
        &#8226;Disconnection: Unintentional :( Any disconnection
        between match players due to System , Network , PC,
        and/or Power problems/issues) will be dealt accordingly.

        </item>
        <item>All THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block Ground Floor and Kalpana Chawla Labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shivansh Bhatnagar - 8285842697\n &#8226;Shriya Goel - 8860390015</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gaming_6">
        <item>TEKKEN</item>
        <item>&#8226;
            will update soon.

        </item>
        <item>
        MATCH FORMAT:\n
        &#8226; Matches would be played on LAN.\n
        &#8226; Match Type will be TEAM BATTLE MODE.\n
        &#8226; For each fight timer would be of 60 seconds.\n
        &#8226; Player is allowed to play with any character except
        GON and DR. B.\n
        &#8226; Every match will be KNOCK OUT.\n
        RULES TO BE FOLLOWED:\n
        &#8226; Keyboard will be provided for playing, however
        players can bring and use their own Gamepad.\n
        &#8226; Unnecessarily PAUSING the game will results in
        disqualification.\n
        &#8226; All equipment provided should be handled carefully,
        any contestant found damaging equipment will be
        immediately disqualified.4. Any excuses attributed to mobile rings, itches,
        sneezing etc. will not be tolerated.\n
        &#8226; If a participant wishes to change the controller
        configuration it shall be done before the match, once
        the match has begun no change will be allowed.\n
        &#8226; In case of any technical problem match will be
        restarted.\n
        &#8226; In case of any conflict, organizer’s decision will be
        final.\n
        &#8226; If anyone found cheating/disobeying the rule, will be
        disqualified.\n
        &#8226; On the spot registration will be done only 15th and 16th October
        </item>
        <item>All THREE DAYS</item>
        <item>Ramanujam Block Ground Floor and Kalpana Chawla Labs</item>
        <item>&#8226;J.Vignesh - 9810503229\n &#8226;Pragya Garg - 8826462145</item>

    </string-array>
    <!--TECH ME..................................................................................................-->
    <string name="about_me">this is description about ME.</string>

    <string-array name="me_1">
        <item>Kryptos\n
(Mystery of Words)</item>
        <item>
&#8226;The event is about a quiz which will be based on basic automobile engineering objective type questions. But as the name of event “KRYPTOS” reflects its sense so it would contain some mystery of words.
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; Use of cell phone is prohibited during the quiz.\n
&#8226; Quiz will be in 2 rounds</item>
        <item>15 October\n 10:00am to 12:00pm</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall 2 B-Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Suvin Varghese - 8587920072 \n &#8226;Disha </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="me_2">
        <item>BUOYANT\n
(Experience the space)</item>
        <item>
       &#8226;    We have reached to the space but still we lag to transport any kind of object
to in or out of the space center. Since the space is full of unpredictable
events and disturbance with zero gravity, it becomes quite difficult to
handle the robot used for transportation. As a natural simulator, water
resembles most to the space. So if we are able to control our robot under
water, it would be easy to understand the functioning in the space. So the
event is to build a manually controlled rover which can transverse a 3 D
underwater space simulating tunnel to complete several tasks in least
possible time. The rover must have a picking mechanism which will help in
completing the task described below
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; The participant need to register as a team and team should have a Team
name and team captain.\n
&#8226; Maximum members in a team should not be more than 4.\n
&#8226; The participants are expected to play fair, in any other case; the entire
team will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; Team GENERO have the authority to take the final decisions. No argues
will be entertained\n
&#8226; Participation certificate will be provided.\n
Rover Specification\n
&#8226; Rover size must not exceed 30cm x 30 cm x 30 cm.\n
&#8226; It must have a picking mechanism whose size must be within the total
length of the rover.\n
&#8226; Use of any mechanism for movement of rover underwater is allowed.
&#8226; Manual controller (wired/wireless) must be used.\n
Task Statement\n
&#8226; The rover need to start from starting position.\n
&#8226; As the event will start, rover will have to transverse to a 3-D maze and
will have to pick a block of 50mmx50mmx50mm using picking\n
mechanism. After picking the block, rover need to change its level inside
the water and has to carry the block with Itself to the point where it has
to place the block.\n
&#8226; The rover has to transport 2 blocks in its whole journey.\n
&#8226; Maximum time allowed to finish the task is 15 minutes.\n
&#8226; The length of the wire (for wired control) should be long enough to cover
the whole track and wire should remain slack during the complete run.\n</item>
        <item>17 October\n 12:00pm to 3:00pm</item>
        <item>Nescafe Ground</item>
        <item>&#8226;Prashant Pandey - 8447862896 \n &#8226;Shubham Saini - 9456861575</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="me_3">
        <item>NEED FOR WAVES (BOAT RACE)</item>
        <item>
&#8226;The team has to build a boat which can transverse a maze that will contain
hurdles.\n
Boat Specification\n
&#8226; The maximum dimension of the boat can be 30 cm x 30 cm x 30 cm (l x
b x h).\n
&#8226; The boat may be wired or wireless.\n
&#8226; Use of any mechanism for propulsion is allowed.\n
&#8226; The length of the wire (for wired bots) should be long enough to cover
the whole track and wire should remain slack during the complete run.\n
&#8226; Each team must prepare its own power sources. Only 220V volt AC
sources will be provided at the arena, but can only be used in the form of
maximum 24 volt DC voltage.\n
&#8226; Readymade toy boats are not allowed.\n
Team specification and eligibility\n
&#8226; A team may consist of a maximum of 4 members. Students from
different educational institutes can form a team.\n
&#8226; Participants should carry with them valid identity cards.\n

        </item>
        <item>&#8226; Any team that is not ready at the time specified will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; The machines would be checked for their safety before the run and
would be discarded if found unsafe for other participants and spectators.\n
&#8226; ‘Organizing teams’ decision shall be final and binding to all.\n
&#8226; Any boat not conforming to the specifications provided will be instantly
disqualified.\n
&#8226; Any boat which damages the arena will be disqualified.\n
&#8226; Flying (using air foil, helium balloons etc.) is not allowed.\n
&#8226; There will be two timing based rounds, the top 5 teams having the best
timing shall proceed in the second round.\n
&#8226; The level of difficulty in the second round will be greater, e.g. – waves,
extra barrios etc.\n
&#8226; The organizers reserve the right to change any or all of the above rules as
they see fit.\n
&#8226; Change in rules, if any, will be highlighted on the website and notified to
the registered participants.\n
</item>
        <item>15 October \n
        11:00am to 1:00pm</item>
        <item>Fountain A- Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vivek Rawat - 8826780957 \n &#8226;Suraj Rawat - 7838035397</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="me_4">
        <item>Fate the aviate\n
(Cheers to air)</item>
        <item>
           &#8226;The water rocketry challenge is a competition to build a rocket powered by
pressurized water. The competition focuses on designing aerodynamically
better rockets that would be capable of targeted flights when launched at a
particular angle from the horizontal. The participants need to study the
basics of rocketry and come up with their own designs.\n
Problem Statement:\n
&#8226;Design and Build a water rocket which can be launched at any angle with
respect to the horizontal. The teams will be participating in two rounds and
the winners will be decided on the basis of rules given below.\n
General Instructions-\n
&#8226; The participant need to register as a team and team should have a Team
name and team captain.\n
&#8226; Maximum members in a team should not be more than 4.\n
&#8226; The participants are expected to play fair, in any other case; the entire
team will be\n
&#8226; Team GENERO have the authority to take the final decisions. No argues
will be entertained.\n
&#8226; Participation certificate will be provided.\n
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; The rocket shall be made of low density material like plastic. Metals and
other high density materials are strictly prohibited.\n
&#8226; The water rocket must be single stage.\n
&#8226; It must not carry any sharp edges for safety purpose.(This may led to the
rejection of team.)\n
&#8226; Only water provided by the organizer must be used as a propellant.\n
&#8226; The rocket must be able to sustain air pressure of 90 psi.\n
&#8226; The launcher or releasing mechanism must be of sufficiently sturdy
construction to ensure a repeatable and predictable launch direction.\n
&#8226; Launcher should be adjustable at any angle in between 30-90 degrees.\n
&#8226; Launcher will be provided within the event by core team in adverse
condition but it would charge some penalty of points.\n</item>
        <item>16 October \n 12:00pm to 3:00pm</item>
        <item>Back Ground</item>
        <item>&#8226;Vikas Chauhan - 9971685069 \n &#8226;Arun Kumar</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="me_5">
        <item>TECH-LE-FUTURE</item>
        <item>
          &#8226; The event is technical presentation in which the team has to present the
paper. The event will provide a platform for the creative minds to share
thoughts about the future and will help individual recognize their
outstanding potential as a presenter.\n
General guide lines\n
&#8226; Physical model is considered as a positive approach in the judging
process.\n
&#8226; Please bring a report at the time of presentation.\n
&#8226; Please bring your own laptops.\n
&#8226; A platform is provided for the presentation which will provide a better
environment for the presenter.\n
&#8226; The decision made by judges is final, if anyone found not following the
instructions sated here and provided by us is considered to have negative
marking.\n
&#8226; Please provide an abstract prior to the presentation with names on
sunny.12me115@abes.ac.in.\n
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; There should be 1 or maximum of 2 members in a team.\n
&#8226; Time allotted for the presentation is 10 min and for questionnaire round
is 2 min.\n
&#8226; Make sure to be in proper formal attire during presentation.\n
&#8226; The topic should be strictly technical but can be of any branch\n</item>
        <item>16 october\n 10:00am to 12:00pm</item>
        <item>Seminar Hall- 2 B-Block</item>
        <item>&#8226;Sunny Ujjain - 7503674750 \n &#8226;Prakhar Gupta</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="me_6">
        <item>Schrottplatz\n
Treasure From Trash</item>
        <item>
        &#8226;This event will be fun for those who can think out of the box. Reduce,
Reuse, Recycle — three great ways YOU can eliminate waste and protect
your environment! And this event focus on the single R i.e. Reuse. Today by
leading technologies, it have been a keen interest of scholars to find out the
new products. But every time we have limited resources. This is what the
motive of the event. In “Junkyard” the teams will be checked on the basis of
their innovative skills and the use of their knowledge in real world. Teams
with limited resources and time have to find out the product which have
some type of utility.\n
Problem Statement\n
&#8226;Trash item will be provided to the teams by an organizing committee on the
day of event. Teams have to convert that trash into some useful product.
Everything will be provided, teams are not allowed to use anything they
bring from home.\n
        </item>
        <item>&#8226; Team can have max of three players.\n
&#8226; Time allotted per team is 2 1/2 hrs. No extra time will be awarded.\n
&#8226; It will be single day event.\n
&#8226; Teams can be inter-branch of same college.\n
&#8226; Use of internet is strictly prohibited.\n
&#8226; Final decision will be given by the judges. On the basis of novelty of
the product.\n
&#8226; All the instructions will be given at the center at the time of event.\n
&#8226; Please bring your own pencil, pen, colors, or markers.\n
&#8226; Bring your ID card.\n
</item>
        <item>15 October \n 11:00am to 3:00pm</item>
        <item>Mechanical Workshop</item>
        <item>&#8226;Srijan Nigam - 9717724266 \n &#8226;Pawan Pandey - 9958870113</item>
    </string-array>


    <!-- special attraction -->
    <string-array name="special_1">
        <item>Battle Of Bands</item>
        <item> Description\n

&#8226;Battle of the Bands is a contest in which two or more bands compete for the title of "best band".
            The winner is determined by the judging panel based on multiple parameters.\n

&#8226;Being a special attraction for the second day in our three day long festival,
            it will feature several bands playing live in front of the audience.
            The winning band receives a prize that usually includes cash and coupons and other hampers. </item>
        <item>&#8226; Bands must submit the fee with the entry form found on Genero 2015 website else through the
registration desk at ABES Engineering College. In case of any queries, please mail us at
genero@abes.ac.in or contact the event head.\n
&#8226; Bands must be prepared to play a set of at least 10 minutes but not to exceed 20 minutes or at
the discretion of the Organizing Committee (the sets may be altered based on the size of entries).\n
&#8226; For every minute exceeding the 20 minutes limit, the band will be penalized 5 points from
their total score until the total time recorded equals to 25 minutes.\n
&#8226; Judging is done on a 1 -10 scale by 3 judges and includes category as song selection, crowd
response, co-ordination amongst multiple others.\n
&#8226; The band members should carry their college identity cards or any other identity proof along
with them.\n
&#8226; A band should include a minimum of 3 members in it.\n
&#8226; Only standard 5 pc. Drum kit will be provided with sound. All other instruments to be brought
by the participants themselves.\n
Note: - Though guitar processors are allowed, NO voice modulators or anything relevant is permitted.\n
&#8226; Entry fee shall be 2000/- (Rupees Two Thousand Only) per band.\n
&#8226; Judges’ decision will be final and binding.\n
&#8226; For any other query, please contact the organizers.\n
&#8226; Visit http://www.genero15.com/bob.php and register using the PayU money button.\n </item>
        <item>16 October\n 5:00pm</item>
        <item>Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226;Tushar Mohan</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="special_2">
        <item>Live Concert of Falak Shabir</item>
        <item> Description\n

It\’s the Star Night! Falak Shabir performs live and loud in Genero 2015.\n A never before experience
            with the singer firing up the stage with his tracks like mera mann, sajna, intezar, soniye,
            judaai…and that\’s not all! DJ Maq spinning the best on the decks, it\'s going to be ONE EPIC PARTY!</item>
        <item>Will update soon</item>
        <item>&#8226;17 October</item>
        <item>&#8226;Back Stage</item>
        <item>&#8226;Shashank Shandilya \n
            &#8226;Tushar Mohan \n
            &#8226;Saransh Tiwari \n
            &#8226;Anubhav Rai \n
            &#8226;Vishal Chauhan \n
            &#8226;Pranav Saxena \n
            &#8226;Amzad Khan</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="special_4">
        <item>Asmita Theatre</item>
        <item>For Adding feathers and gracing the occasion of Genero\'15 we have  ASMITA, one of the leading Hindi theatre groups in the country stands committed to aesthetically innovative and socially relevant theatre. Since its inception in 1993, ASMITA has carved a niche for itself in the Indian theatre scene by staging plays of varied socio-political interest while not losing out mass appeal. The group takes up contemporary issues to underline the contours of our time while providing the best of entertainment.The group has 62 productions to its credit and on an average has been performing for about 60 nights a year. All these plays have been directed by ASMITA\'s Resident Director Arvind Gaur. For ASMITA, theatre has a purpose of awakening the audience to contemporary issues and creating a dialogue on prevailing social problems. Asmita Theatre group is also involved in street Theatre Movement. Group has performed dozens of street plays on different Socio-political issues.</item>
        <item>For Adding feathers and gracing the occasion of Genero\'15 we have  ASMITA, one of the leading Hindi theatre groups in the country stands committed to aesthetically innovative and socially relevant theatre. Since its inception in 1993, ASMITA has carved a niche for itself in the Indian theatre scene by staging plays of varied socio-political interest while not losing out mass appeal. The group takes up contemporary issues to underline the contours of our time while providing the best of entertainment.The group has 62 productions to its credit and on an average has been performing for about 60 nights a year. All these plays have been directed by ASMITA\'s Resident Director Arvind Gaur. For ASMITA, theatre has a purpose of awakening the audience to contemporary issues and creating a dialogue on prevailing social problems. Asmita Theatre group is also involved in street Theatre Movement. Group has performed dozens of street plays on different Socio-political issues.</item>
        <item>15 October \n from 6PM </item>
        <item>Auditorium</item>
        <item>Vishal Chauhan - 8587844808</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="special_3">
        <item>Dalal Street</item>
        <item>will be upgraded soon</item>
        <item>will be upgraded soon</item>
        <item>will be upgraded soon</item>
        <item>will be upgraded soon</item>
        <item>will be upgraded soon</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="title_activity_developers">Developers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_genero_app_referrals">GeneroAppReferrals</string>

</resources>